Narrator: 1
A: I like the multiculturalism.
People from all over the world live in the US,
and we live together happily. Usually.
Narrator: 2
B: For me, it’s the language.
English is international.
I speak English.
You speak English.
I’m lucky – I don’t have communication problems.
Narrator: 3
C: I like the coffee.
I have a large cup every day.
When I’m in a hurry,
I go to the drive-through and buy it from my car.
Narrator: 4
D: I love the freedom.
I wear what I want.
I say what I want.
I do what I want.
Narrator: 5
E: One thing I really like is the sports.
I like all kinds, but I really like basketball.
My favorite team is the Golden State Warriors.
I watch their games on TV.
Narrator: 6
F: I like the freeways.
They have a lot of car lanes and are very fast.
It’s really easy to drive from one place to another.
Narrator: 7
G: I really like the weather here, especially in the fall.
A good fall day is cool, but not too cold.
Sometimes it rains, but it doesn’t rain every day.
Narrator: 8
H: I love the food.
My boyfriend makes really good burritos,
and the US has great Mexican restaurants!